All right. So in the last video, we had a look at the basic skeleton of every Java program that is every Java program now has to have the class and the public static wide main and we went ahead and printed our first line on screen.
So we're going to take the discussion forward and try to do a few more things that would just help you to get up and running with writing Java code.
And this is just a distributed out of print ln, which just prints a new line on screen in Java and in the recent in the recent update to the language, we even have a shorter, succinct way to do that.
And again, I'm just going to put that all together in one of the videos ahead, but for now it's just going to follow what you're going to see in in the majority of the cases where you would write code where you would read other scored or where a lot of code is already written and that has a class as a structure, the main method and the print ln as you're seeing on my screen.
And if you would want this to be, let's say a second line to be printed, all you have to do is just copy paste it and the shortcut for doing that is I had the cursor placed on this line.
I exactly wanted it this to be on the second line.
So rather than saying control C and we we even have a shorter way, there's just command D right.
So you just press command D and it was just copy pasted and now I'll just go ahead and just say on the next line.
And you just go on and run this or just hit under the shortcut because we should try to use the mouse as less as we can and the keyboard should be should be a primary device for navigating and the shortcut on my system, it would be the same on your system is control R.
Which is gone and hit this and you're seeing that we got the next line on in fact the next line as well, because unlike sees printf and C++ C out when you have to put in a escape character, which by the way on Java as well, but print line print aliens stands for print line, it has the escape character for next line bundled with it.
You saw this on the next line and if you would have used a escape character like you would have used on in a C++ or C environment, then obviously you would get two lines in between I'll just go on and run this again control R is the shortcut as you're seeing that it left one more line.
So that is just printing things out with a print ln.